<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Class Homepage</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Class Homepage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Categories</title>
      <link>/docs/grading/categories/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/grading/categories/</guid>
      <description>Categories # Assignments (50%) # There will be four assignments. Each one is designed to improve and test your understanding of the materials. Assignments will have both programming and written analysis components.&#xA;We have 4 big assignments in total. The reason we do not call them projects is because our class has a project as well. Consider each assignment as one individual big project. Assignments take time to finish them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collection</title>
      <link>/docs/resources/collection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/resources/collection/</guid>
      <description>Resource Collection # Helpful Texts # No textbook will be required for this course, however you are strongly encouraged to complete the readings indicated for each class. You may also find the following books very helpful:&#xA;Learning from data, by Yaser S. Abu-Mostafa Pattern recognition and machine learning, by Christopher Bishop Machine learning, by Tom Mitchell Data Mining: Concepts and Techniques, by Jiawei Han, Micheline Kamber, and Jian Pei The Elements of Statistical Learning, by Trevor Hastie, Robert Tibshirani, and Jerome Friedman Deep Learning, by Ian Goodfellow, Yoshua Bengio, and Aaron Courville Other resources, such as machine learning toolboxes and datasets, will be provided throughout the course.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Course Overview</title>
      <link>/docs/course-info/course-overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/course-info/course-overview/</guid>
      <description>Course Overview # Important&#xA;CSE students should note that CS 7641 is not allowed as a substitute for the CSE core course CSE 6740, and that they cannot get credit for both CSE 6740 and CS 7641. This course introduces techniques in machine learning with an emphasis on algorithms and their applications to real-world data. We will investigate the following question: how to computationally extract useful knowledge from data for decision making and task support!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General</title>
      <link>/docs/guidelines/general/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/guidelines/general/</guid>
      <description>General # Attendance # Our class will be offered on campus for both Undergrad (4641) and Grad (7641). Lectures might be recorded IF class has the recording system. Any class that I am able to record [which sometimes does not work even if we have the recording system in place], I will make it available to all students (both undergrad and grad) by the end of the day. The attendance is required for both undergrad and grad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proposal</title>
      <link>/docs/grading/project-breakdown/proposal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/grading/project-breakdown/proposal/</guid>
      <description>Proposal (5%) # The primary goal of the proposal is to identify a problem that can be solved with machine learning. This includes finding and/or creating a dataset as well as developing a plan for the semester.&#xA;Note: As part of research, it is natural that the project may change from the original proposed. Please be sure to document and justify these changes in the midterm and final report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instructor and TAs</title>
      <link>/docs/course-info/instructors-and-tas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/course-info/instructors-and-tas/</guid>
      <description>Instructors and TAs # Instructor # Max Mahdi Roozbahani mahdir@gatech.edu https://mahdi-roozbahani.github.io/ Head TAs # Gururaj Deshpande gurudesh@gatech.edu Will Spaeth jspaeth7@gatech.edu Mohammad Taher mtaher3@gatech.edu TAs # Krish Nathan knathan8@gatech.edu Ziyuan Cao zcao300@gatech.edu Luting Wang lwang797@gatech.edu Nouf Al Soghyar nsoghyar3@gatech.edu William Runyon wrunyon3@gatech.edu Madhuri Singh msingh365@gatech.edu Parisa Babolhavaeji pbabolhavaeji3@gatech.edu Andrew H Zhang azhang377@gatech.edu David Williams dwilliams402@gatech.edu Gautam Ramesh gramesh32@gatech.edu Harsha D Karanth hkaranth3@gatech.edu Nigam Katta nkatta9@gatech.edu Shiva Ramaswami sramaswami30@gatech.edu Suraj Karthic skarthic3@gatech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Midterm Checkpoint</title>
      <link>/docs/grading/project-breakdown/midterm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/grading/project-breakdown/midterm/</guid>
      <description>Midterm Checkpoint (10%) # This is a checkpoint to make sure that you have had major progress in your project. By this point, at least one machine learning model should be implemented and evaluated. Results should be presented using visualizations and quantitative metrics. You will add information to your proposal to create your midterm report.&#xA;Note: As part of research, it is natural that the project may change from the original proposed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Office Hours</title>
      <link>/docs/guidelines/office-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/guidelines/office-hours/</guid>
      <description>Office Hours # Overview # Office hours will start on the second week of classes in a hybrid mode for both online and in-person. Please follow the instruction on this Excel Sheet [Grad|Undergrad] ​to signup for a 15-minutes slot with one of the TAs. You need to add your name and question of interest. If you require more than 15 minutes, please advise the TAs.&#xA;Be aware that some TAs have physical hours while others have virtual hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Course Schedule</title>
      <link>/docs/course-info/course-schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/course-info/course-schedule/</guid>
      <description>Schedule # Important&#xA;All deadline and due dates in this course will be at 23:59 EST.&#xA;Scroll horizontally to see the full schedule table on mobile devices Astericks (*) indicate that the lecture slides/notes are available.&#xA;Week Dates Topics Homework Quizzes Project Readings 1 Jan 8-12 *Course Overview (L1) *Data analysis toolbox - P1 (L2) Q0 - L1,2 (Warmup) GT Honor Code; [Debugging Common Errors in NumPy](/other/Debugging Common Errors in NumPy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diversity &amp; Inclusion</title>
      <link>/docs/guidelines/diversity-and-inclusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/guidelines/diversity-and-inclusion/</guid>
      <description>Diversity &amp;amp; Inclusion # Just as machine learning algorithms cannot accomplish complex tasks if trained on datasets of limited variability, our course cannot be successful without appreciating the diversity of our students. In this class we aim to create an environment where all voices are valued, respecting the diversity of gender, sexuality, age, socioeconomic status, ability, ethnicity, race, and culture. We always welcome suggestions that can help us achieve this goal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Final Report</title>
      <link>/docs/grading/project-breakdown/final/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/grading/project-breakdown/final/</guid>
      <description>Final Report (15%) # The final report should present and compare at least 3 models that you have developed throughout the semester. Results should be presented using visualizations and quantitative metrics with a heavy focus on comparing the performance and tradeoffs of each approach. You will add information to your midterm to create your final report.&#xA;Note: As part of research, it is natural that the project may change from the original proposed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/guidelines/covid-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/guidelines/covid-19/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
